A Guide to the Virginia Dietetic Association Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
Historical Collections, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library, University of Virginia
Virginia Dietetic Association Collection, 1929-2004
Historical Collections, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library, University of Virginia
MS-38
The collection consists of 30,500 pages in 69 boxes 5"x10.5"x15.5" and 2 folio boxes 18.5"x3"x15", 31 linear feet of processed materials.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The Virginia Dietetic Association(VDA) donated the organization's papers to the University of Virginia Health Sciences Library circa 1990.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Virginia Dietetic Association (VDA) is an organization of food and nutrition professionals in Virginia. The Association was organized on February 14, 1929 and became one of the American Dietetic Association's 53 state associations in April 1929. Since its foundation, the Virginia Dietetic Association has provided the direction and leadership for quality dietetic practice, education, and research for the improvement of the health and nutrition in Virginia. The membership of the Virginia Dietetic Association includes registered dietitians, registered dietetic technicians, consultants, researchers, and students. The Association started with nine dietitians and steadily increased its membership to the present number of 1,500 as of April 2009.
The Virginia Dietetic Association has five sub-district associations: Blue Ridge Dietetic Association, Northern Virginia Dietetic Association, Richmond Dietetic Association, Southwest Dietetic Association and Tidewater Dietetic Association. The five district associations regularly meet and work closely together in support of the Virginia Dietetic Association in various campaigns and activities.
Scope and Content Information
The Virginia Dietetic Association Collection contains a various range of important information on VDA from 1929 to 2004. Materials include minute books, financial records, Presidents' files, scrapbooks, journals and newsletters, papers, legislative documents, correspondence, newspaper articles, pamphlets, and photos. The collection also includes materials on other organizations such as the American Dietetic Association (ADA), Indiana Dietetic Association, Puerto Rico Dietetic Association, Ohio Dietetic Association, and the North Carolina Licensed Practical Nurse Association.
Contents List
- Dietetic Association of Virginia: Application for State Association Affiliation, February 14, 1929, AD(1) (Box-folder 001:001)
  Application Form
- Dietetic Association of Virginia: By-laws, 1929, TD(4) (Box-folder 001:002)
- Dietetic Association of Virginia: Minutes, 1929, TD(6) (Box-folder 001:003)
- Dietetic Association of Virginia: Minutes, 1930, TD(4), AD(2) (Box-folder 001:004)
- Dietetic Association of Virginia: Minute, 1931, TD(1) (Box-folder 001:005)
- Virginia State Dietetics Association: Minutes, 1932, TD(2) (Box-folder 001:006)
- Virginia State Dietetics Association: Minutes, 1933, TD(4) (Box-folder 001:006)
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Minutes, 1934, TD(10), AD(4) (Box-folder 001:008)
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Minutes, President's Reports and Treasurer's Reports, 1935, TD(23), AD(3) (Box-folder 001:009)
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Minutes, 1936, TD(18) (Box-folder 001:010)
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Reports on the History of the Association, 1936, TD(18) (Box-folder 001:011)
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Letter from Frances Helen Zeigler, President of the Graduate Nurses Association of Virginia, March 13, 1936, TD(1) (Box-folder 001:012)
- Southwestern Virginia Dietetic Association: Application for Local Association Affiliation, March 14, 1936, TD(2) (Box-folder 001:013)
- Southwestern Virginia Dietetic Association: Constitution and By-laws, 1936, TD(5) (Box-folder 001:014)
- Convention of the American Dietetic Association in Richmond, Virginia, October 17-23, 1937, TD(19), AD(11), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 001:015)
  Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John Powell Concert Tickets, October 19, 1937, TD(19), AD(11) (Box-folder 001:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Minutes, 1937-1938, TD(20) (Box-folder 001:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Minutes, 1939, TD(33) (Box-folder 001:018)
- Virginia Hospital Association News(Volume I, Number 2), January, 1939, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 001:019)
- Report of the Richmond Dietetic Association, April 22, 1939, TD(2) (Box-folder 001:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Report: "High Lights in the History of the Virginia State Dietetic Association", 1939, TD(3) (Box-folder 001:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Report: "Dietary Problem from Viewpoint of Administrator", 1939, TD(2) (Box-folder 001:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Report: "Dietetics from the College Students' Viewpoint", 1939, TD(2) (Box-folder 001:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Report: "Recent Trends in Placement Possibilities for Dietitians", 1939, TD(2) (Box-folder 001:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Report: "Dietetics and Its Relation to Health", 1939, TD(2) (Box-folder 001:025)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Report: "When the Dietitian Buys Food For An Institution", 1939, TD(2) (Box-folder 001:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Report: "Health Problems of the South", 1939, TD(8) (Box-folder 001:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Minutes and Treasurer's Reports, 1940, TD(43) (Box-folder 001:028)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Minutes and Reports, 1941, TD(9), AD(7) (Box-folder 001:029)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Minute and Report, 1942, TD(2) (Box-folder 001:030)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Minutes and Treasurer's Report, 1943, TD(5) (Box-folder 001:031)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Minutes, Reports and Meeting Notification Letters, 1942, TDoc, Pamphlets (2) (Box-folder 001:032)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Minute and Treasurer's Report, 1957 - 1958, TD(2) (Box-folder 001:033)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Minute and Treasurer's Reports, 1946, TD(3) (Box-folder 001:034)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Minutes, 1947-1958, TD(17) (Box-folder 001:035)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Minutes and Letter, 1959, TD(5) (Box-folder 001:036)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Presidents and Officers, 1929-1959, TD(35), Photos(21), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 001:037)
  Membership Lists, CVs
- Virginia Dietetic Association Report("The History of the Virginia Dietetic Association"), 1951, TD(2) (Box-folder 001:038)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1934-1939, Scrapbook (Box-folder 002:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1941, Scrapbook (Box-folder 002:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1942-1953, Scrapbook (Box-folder 002:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1954, Scrapbook (Box-folder 003:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1955, Scrapbook (Box-folder 003:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1956, Scrapbook (Box-folder 003:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1957, Scrapbook (Box-folder 003:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1958, Scrapbook (Box-folder 004:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1959, Scrapbook (Box-folder 004:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1960, Scrapbook (Box-folder 004:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1961, Scrapbook (Box-folder 004:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1962, Scrapbook (Box-folder 005:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1963, Scrapbook (Box-folder 005:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1964, Scrapbook (Box-folder 005:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1965, Scrapbook (Box-folder 005:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1966, Scrapbook (Box-folder 006:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1967, Scrapbook (Box-folder 006:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1968, Scrapbook (Box-folder 006:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1969, Scrapbook (Box-folder 007:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1970, Scrapbook (Box-folder 007:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1971, Scrapbook (Box-folder 007:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1972, Scrapbook (Box-folder 008:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1973, Scrapbook (Box-folder 008:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1974, Scrapbook (Box-folder 008:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1975, Scrapbook (Box-folder 009:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1976, Scrapbook (Box-folder 009:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1977-1978, Scrapbook (Box-folder 009:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1978-1979, Scrapbook (Box-folder 009:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1979-1980, Scrapbook (Box-folder 009:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook, 1980-1981, Scrapbook (Box-folder 009:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Tidewater Dietetic Association, 1983-1984, TDoc(9) (Box-folder 010:001)
  Letters, Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Roanoke Dietetic Association, 1983-1984, TDoc(6) (Box-folder 010:002)
  Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Richmond Dietetic Association, 1983-1984, TDoc(13) (Box-folder 010:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Blue Ridge Dietetic Association, 1983-1984, TDoc(4) (Box-folder 010:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association, 1983-1984, TDoc(2) (Box-folder 010:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: ADA Courier, 1983-1984, Newsletters(5) (Box-folder 010:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newspaper Articles, 1983-1984, Newspaper Articles (Box-folder 010:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board and Council, 1983-1984, TD(11) (Box-folder 010:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Spring Meeting and Fall Meeting, 1983-1984, Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 010:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: President-Elect Nominations, 1983-1984, AD(9) (Box-folder 010:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Secretary Nominations, 1983-1984, AD(11) (Box-folder 010:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Delegate Nominations, 1983-1984, AD(3) (Box-folder 010:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Public Relations Director Nominations, 1983-1984, AD(11) (Box-folder 010:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Nominating Committee Nominations, 1983-1984, AD(14) (Box-folder 010:014)
- irginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Chairman-Elect Nominations, 1983-1984, AD(14) (Box-folder 010:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Chairman-Elect, Council on Practice Nominations, 1983-1984, AD(8) (Box-folder 010:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: CVs for Nominations, 1983-1984, TD(37), AD(19), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 010:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board and Council, 1984-1985, TD(11) (Box-folder 010:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board and Council Meeting(11/10/1984), 1984-1985, TD(12) (Box-folder 010:019)
  Minutes, Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(2/2/1985), 1984-1985, TD(35), AD(2) (Box-folder 010:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board and Council Meeting(2/9/1985), 1984-1985, TD(5) (Box-folder 010:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board and Council Meeting(4/16/1985), 1984-1985, TD(4), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 010:022)
  Minutes, Meeting Pamphlet
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board and Council Meeting(9/7/1985), 1984-1985, TD(43), AD(13) (Box-folder 010:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: CVs for Nominations, 1984-1985, Photos(4) (Box-folder 010:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Tidewater Dietetic Association, 1984-1985, TD(3) (Box-folder 010:025)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Richmond Dietetic Association, 1984-1985, TD(2) (Box-folder 010:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association, 1984-1985, TD(5), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 010:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Blueridge Dietetic Association, 1984-1985, TD(3) (Box-folder 010:028)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Roanoke Dietetic Association, 1984-1985, TD(3) (Box-folder 010:029)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: National Nutrition Month, 1984-1985, TD(3) (Box-folder 010:030)
  Certificate of Recognition
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Poll Concerning One VS. Two Meetings Per Year, 1984-1985, TD, AD (Box-folder 010:031)
  Reports, Letters, Memorandum
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Recognized Young Dietitian of the Year Award, 1984-1985, TD(35), Newspaper Articles(2) (Box-folder 010:032)
  Reports, Letters, Guidelines, Resumes
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Recommendation for Brenda Numerof as a Candidate for the Young Dietitian of the Year Award, 1984-1985, TD(26), Newspaper Article(1) (Box-folder 010:033)
  Reports, Letters, Resumes
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newspaper Articles, 1984-1985, Newspaper Articles (Box-folder 010:034)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Officers and Membership List, 1985-1986, TD(22) (Box-folder 011:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newsletters, 1985-1986, Newsletters(3) (Box-folder 011:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Annual Financial Reports, 1985-1986, TD(31) (Box-folder 011:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Long-Range Plan and Goal, 1985-1986, TD(12) (Box-folder 011:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: ADA House of Delegates Meeting- Delegate's Report (November 1985), 1985-1986, TD(5) (Box-folder 011:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(November 6, 1985), 1985-1986, TD(12) (Box-folder 011:006)
  Minutes, Reports, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Fall Conference- Nutrition "Quality Not Quackery"(November 6-8, 1985), 1985-1986, TD(2) (Box-folder 011:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(February 1, 1986), 1985-1986, TD(43), AD(1) (Box-folder 011:008)
  Minutes, Reports, Letters, Bylaws, Map
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(April 2, 1986), 1985-1986, TD(60), Newspaper Article(1) (Box-folder 011:009)
  Minutes, Reports, By-laws, Letters, Order Form, Registration Forms, Flyers
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Richmond Dietetic Association, 1985-1986, TD(4) (Box-folder 011:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Roanoke Dietetic Association, 1985-1986, TD(2), AD(1) (Box-folder 011:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Tidewater Dietetic Association, 1985-1986, TD(4) (Box-folder 011:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Hearing on House Joint Resolutions 12(Operators of X-Ray Equipment) and 150(Dietitians and Nutritionists) on June 12, 1985-1986, TD(5) (Box-folder 011:013)
  Reports, Letters, By-law
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newspaper Articles and Photos, 1985-1986, Newspaper Clippings(2), Photos(2) (Box-folder 011:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Action Plan for 1987, 1986-1987, TD(11), Newsletter(1), Flyer(1) (Box-folder 011:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(October 8, 1986), 1986-1987, TD(11) (Box-folder 011:016)
  Reports, Minutes
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(November 11, 1986), 1986-1987, TD(19) (Box-folder 011:017)
  Reports, Minutes, Registration Forms, Flyers, Letters, By-laws
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(December 10, 1986), 1986-1987, TD(15), AD(2) (Box-folder 011:018)
  Reports, Minutes, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board and Council, 1986-1987, TD(11) (Box-folder 011:019)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Bylaws, 1986-1987, TD(13) (Box-folder 011:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(January 31, 1987), 1986-1987, TD(34), AD(1) (Box-folder 011:021)
  Reports, Minutes, Letters, Newsletter Article
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(April 8, 1986), 1986-1987, TD(68), AD(2), Map(1) (Box-folder 011:022)
  Reports, Registration Form, Letters, Seminar Announcement
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(September 12, 1986), 1986-1987, TD(8) (Box-folder 011:023)
  Minutes, Ballot
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: ADA Newsletters, 1986-1987, TLS (1), TDoc (20, TMemo (1), Pamphlet(3) Newsletters(2) (Box-folder 011:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: ADA/USA-Today Post-Holiday Hotline, 1986-1987, TD(11), AD(1) (Box-folder 011:025)
  Reports, Forms, Map
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Tidewater Dietetic Association, 1986-1987, TD(3) (Box-folder 011:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Richmond Dietetic Association, 1986-1987, TD(8) (Box-folder 011:027)
  Reports, Flyer
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Southwest Virginia Dietetic Association, 1986-1987, TD(1) (Box-folder 011:028)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Reports from the Blue Ridge Dietetic Association, 1986-1987, TD(2) (Box-folder 011:029)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Newsletter, 1986-1987, TD(1), Newsletters(1) (Box-folder 011:030)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Fall Conference(November 11-13, 1987), 1986-1987, TD(7) (Box-folder 011:031)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newspaper Articles, Pamphlets, and ADA Logo Stitch Design, 1986-1987, Newspaper Clippings(2), Pamphlets(3), Promotional Literature(2), Lapel Pin(1) (Box-folder 011:032)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Officers and Membership List, 1976-1977, TD(5) (Box-folder 012:001)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newsletters, 1976-1977, Newsletters(11), Newspaper Articles(2), TD(9) (Box-folder 012:002)
  Letters, Reports, Flyer
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Photos, 1976-1977, Photos(3) (Box-folder 012:003)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Officers and Membership List, 1978-1979, TD(10) (Box-folder 012:004)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newsletters, 1978-1979, Newsletters(6), TD(5) (Box-folder 012:005)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: By-laws, 1978-1979, TD(8) (Box-folder 012:006)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Meetings, 1978-1979, TD(3), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 012:007)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newspaper Articles, 1978-1979, Newspaper Articles(14), TD(7), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 012:008)
  Elementary Menu
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Meetings, 1979-1980, TD(38) (Box-folder 012:009)
  Reports, Minute, Letters
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newsletters, 1979-1980, Newsletters(4) (Box-folder 012:010)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newspaper Articles, 1979-1980, Newspaper Articles(19), TD(4), Flyers(2) (Box-folder 012:011)
  School Lunch Patterns, Book Lists
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Membership List, 1979-1980, TD(2) (Box-folder 012:012)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Officers and Membership List, 1980-1981, TD(17) (Box-folder 012:013)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Pamphlets, 1980-1981, Pamphlets(3) (Box-folder 012:014)
  Saint Luke Institute
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newsletters, 1980-1981, Newsletters(5) (Box-folder 012:015)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Meetings, 1980-1981, TD(43) (Box-folder 012:016)
  Minute, Reports, Letters, Newspaper Articles
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Meetings, 1981-1982, TD(33) (Box-folder 012:017)
  Reports, Newspaper Articles
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Officers and Membership List and Ballot, 1981-1982, TD(18) (Box-folder 012:018)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newsletters, 1981-1982, Newsletters(4) (Box-folder 012:019)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Newsletters, 1982-1983, Newsletters(4) (Box-folder 013:001)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Officers and Membership List, 1982-1983, TD(11) (Box-folder 013:002)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Meetings, 1982-1983, TD(15), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 013:003)
  Minutes, Letters, Reports
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: National Nutrition Month(March 1983), 1982-1983, TD(11), Newspaper Article(1), Flyers(3) (Box-folder 013:004)
  Reports, Letters, Reading List, Recipes
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Third-party Reimbursement Project, 1982-1983, TD(7) (Box-folder 013:005)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: FDA/USDA Research Plan for Evaluating Nutrition Labeling Formats, 1982-1983, TD(4) (Box-folder 013:006)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Officers, Membership List, and Ballot, 1983-1984, TD(15) (Box-folder 013:007)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: VDA Executive Board Meeting(January 21, 1983), 1983-1984, TD(2) (Box-folder 013:008)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(October 26, 1983), 1983-1984, TD(6) (Box-folder 013:009)
  Reports, Letter
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Annual Fall Meeting(November 19, 1983), 1983-1984, TD(19) (Box-folder 013:010)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(December 7, 1983), 1983-1984, TD(14) (Box-folder 013:011)
  Reports, Letters, NDVDA Nominationg Committee Form
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(January 4, 1984), 1983-1984, TD(11) (Box-folder 013:012)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(February 8, 1984), 1983-1984, TD(17) (Box-folder 013:013)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Educational Meeting(February 25, 1984), 1983-1984, TD(1) (Box-folder 013:014)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(March 14, 1984), 1983-1984, TD(12) (Box-folder 013:015)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: VDA Executive Board Meeting(April 4, 1984), 1983-1984, TD(9) (Box-folder 013:016)
  Minute, Reports
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(April 11, 1984), 1983-1984, TD(13), AD(1) (Box-folder 013:017)
  Reports, Letters
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(May 9, 1984), 1983-1984, TD(21), Photo(1) (Box-folder 013:018)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: VDA Licensure Survey (June 1984), 1983-1984, TD(3) (Box-folder 013:019)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(July 21, 1984), 1983-1984, TD(14) (Box-folder 013:020)
- Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: Executive Board Meeting(August 15, 1984), 1983-1984, TD(14) (Box-folder 013:021)